<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Mikael J.Olsson</title>
    <link>https://mikael-ols.github.io/Mikael_J_Olsson_Portfolio/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Mikael J.Olsson</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mikael-ols.github.io/Mikael_J_Olsson_Portfolio/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Project V: www.XGBet.ml</title>
      <link>https://mikael-ols.github.io/Mikael_J_Olsson_Portfolio/post/chapter-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2020 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mikael-ols.github.io/Mikael_J_Olsson_Portfolio/post/chapter-5/</guid>
      <description>XGBet is a spare time project with the aim of beating the bookies. This is done by using machine learning together with a lot of data. As the name suggests, XGBoost is the model used to predict the outcome of the matches. The model is built on over 8000 matches (EPL, La Liga &amp;amp; Bundesliga) with approximately 70 variables.
The return of season 19/29 was 1.557
To visit the website, click here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project IV: Detecting Free Parking Spots Through a R-CNN</title>
      <link>https://mikael-ols.github.io/Mikael_J_Olsson_Portfolio/post/chapter-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mikael-ols.github.io/Mikael_J_Olsson_Portfolio/post/chapter-4/</guid>
      <description>Finding a parking space in a crowded lot can be a really tough and irritating challenge. It is of both the owner of the parking lot and the visitors interest to streamline the process of finding free parking spots. However, many of the solutions requires a lot of equipment, such as sensors on each parking space. But what if one solution only requires a simple camera and some machine learning?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project III: Predicting Mobile Apps Rating</title>
      <link>https://mikael-ols.github.io/Mikael_J_Olsson_Portfolio/post/chapter-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mikael-ols.github.io/Mikael_J_Olsson_Portfolio/post/chapter-3/</guid>
      <description>It feels like everyone have at least one app idea that they say would make milloins. Ironically, I don&amp;rsquo;t know anybody that actually have gone through with their idea. But if they did, would the app be successful? In this project a linear model will be created to predict the rating of mobile apps. The goals of this project are:
Make a model that successfully predicts the rating.
 Find out which variables that are important for predicting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project II: Worlds Most Popular Music(Week 26)</title>
      <link>https://mikael-ols.github.io/Mikael_J_Olsson_Portfolio/post/chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2020 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mikael-ols.github.io/Mikael_J_Olsson_Portfolio/post/chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>Whether I am on the train, the bike, coding or even doing anything at all - I listen to music. However, in the last couple of years when Spotify shows me my most listen to songs, I have realised that the songs are almost 100% from Sweden, the United States or the UK. This has peeked my interest in exploring music from around the world and to see if there is any difference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project I: How Will Premier League End?</title>
      <link>https://mikael-ols.github.io/Mikael_J_Olsson_Portfolio/post/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mikael-ols.github.io/Mikael_J_Olsson_Portfolio/post/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>Premier League, together with almost the rest of the football world, is on hold. It is not clear if the leagues will continue or not. But if they continue, how will they end? In this article I will create a model that predicts the result of the Premier League games left, to complete the league table. Will Liverpool win the league? Will Manchester United qualify to the Champions League? And which teams will be rejected?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>